<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/xsl/atom.xsl" media="all"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/commercial-cleaning/</id>
  <title>The Butler - commercial cleaning</title>
  <subtitle><![CDATA[A ready to use static blog, powered by Cecil.]]></subtitle>
  <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/commercial-cleaning/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/commercial-cleaning/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2020-10-14T18:34:00+02:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>The Butler</name>
    <uri>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/</uri>
  </author>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/draft-example/</id>
    <title>Does high-quality mean high price?</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 id="does-high-quality-mean-high-price">Does high-quality mean high price?</h2>
<p>The high price is a fee for quality, professional team, and the vast range of services provided.</p>
<p>One might get the impression that a high-quality cleaning with a professional team might be expensive, but this is not the case. It is a common misconception that high quality means high price. Quality can be achieved at any price point, and the commercial cleaning industry is a perfect example of this.</p>
<p>The high-quality commercial cleaning company is not just about hiring a professional team of cleaners. It's also about investing in the right equipment and software for your business. This will help you get better results with less time, effort and money spent on training your team and maintaining them.</p>
<p>SHEN has found a way to offer a high-level service without sacrificing price. We came to an understanding that cleaning software can offer a lower cost solution without compromising on quality. This has been made possible by the use of algorithms that can efficiently map and plan routes for cleaners to follow, eliminating the need for human intervention in certain tasks.</p>
<p>We analyze each service in detail and check its quality at each stage. This gives us an opportunity to control quality according to many criteria - completion, schedules, checklists, photos. There is a connection with our manager, who picks up any issue at any stage. We reduce the negative impact of the human factor because our program has a module for employee protection. Additionally, we have worked out all cleaning regulations, algorithms, and norms in each area in order to predict risks so that they have less of an impact on service quality.</p>
<p>This is how you can get your workspace cleaned with a team of professionals for less than you would think and without compromising on quality.</p>
<p>This is what makes SHEN the best commercial cleaning company in the area.</p>
<p>Clean for the best price. Call us.</p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/draft-example/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2020-10-14T18:34:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-12-20T00:14:27+01:00</updated>
  </entry>
</feed>
