<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/xsl/atom.xsl" media="all"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/commercial-cleaning/</id>
  <title>Akulina Nikitina - commercial cleaning</title>
  <subtitle><![CDATA[A wordsmith, storyteller, visionary, and artist.]]></subtitle>
  <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/commercial-cleaning/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/commercial-cleaning/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2022-11-16T18:34:00+01:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Akulina Nikitina</name>
    <uri>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/</uri>
  </author>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/draft-example/</id>
    <title>Does high-quality mean high price?</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 id="does-high-quality-mean-high-price">Does high-quality mean high price?</h2>
<p>The high price is a fee for quality, professional team, and the vast range of services provided. One might get the impression that a high-quality cleaning with a professional team might be expensive, but this is not the case. It is a common misconception that high quality means high price. Quality can be achieved at any price point, and the commercial cleaning industry is a perfect example of this.</p>
<p>The high-quality commercial cleaning company is not just about hiring a professional team of cleaners. It's also about investing in the right equipment and software for your business. This will help you get better results with less time, effort and money spent on training your team and maintaining them.</p>
<p>SHEN has found a way to offer a high-level service without sacrificing price. We came to an understanding that cleaning software can offer a lower cost solution without compromising on quality. This has been made possible by the use of algorithms that can efficiently map and plan routes for cleaners to follow, eliminating the need for human intervention in certain tasks.</p>
<p>We analyze each service in detail and check its quality at each stage. This gives us an opportunity to control quality according to many criteria - completion, schedules, checklists, photos. There is a connection with our manager, who picks up any issue at any stage. We reduce the negative impact of the human factor because our program has a module for employee protection. Additionally, we have worked out all cleaning regulations, algorithms, and norms in each area in order to predict risks so that they have less of an impact on service quality.</p>
<p>This is how you can get your workspace cleaned with a team of professionals for less than you would think and without compromising on quality.</p>
<p>This is what makes SHEN the best commercial cleaning company in the area.</p>
<p>Clean for the best price. Call us.</p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/draft-example/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2022-11-16T18:34:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2022-12-21T19:40:59+01:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/daft-punk/</id>
    <title>Content Plan for Commercial Cleaning Company</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>*﻿Here's the extract from my content plan, which includes several points in few categories, without promotional or discount offers and other important propositions. The artwork featured here was personally designed for the portfolio.</p>
<h2 id="content-plan-for-commercial-cleaning-company">Content plan for commercial cleaning company.</h2>
<ol>
<li>Develop a series of FAQs that address common questions and concerns about commercial cleaning. These could include questions about the safety and effectiveness of cleaning products, the types of services we offer, and the process for booking and scheduling cleaning services. By providing answers to these common questions, we can help potential clients understand our services and make an informed decision.</li>
<li>Create a series of &quot;before and after&quot; photos that showcase the impact of our cleaning services. These photos could include images of dirty and cluttered spaces that have been transformed by our team's cleaning efforts. By highlighting the dramatic improvements that our services can provide, we can show potential clients the value of our services and build trust and credibility.</li>
<li>Develop a series of social media posts that provide tips and advice on maintaining a clean and healthy workspace. These could include quick and easy cleaning hacks, product recommendations, and general advice on how to create a clean and comfortable work environment. By sharing this valuable information on social media, we can engage with potential clients and build our online presence.</li>
<li>Write a series of articles that explore the latest trends and developments in commercial cleaning. These could include articles on new cleaning technologies, eco-friendly cleaning products, and innovative cleaning methods. By staying up-to-date on the latest developments in the industry, we can position ourself as an expert and thought leader in the field of commercial cleaning.</li>
</ol>
<h2 id="ideas-for-articles">Ideas for articles.</h2>
<ol>
<li>The importance of regular cleaning and maintenance. Many businesses may not realize the importance of regular cleaning and maintenance for the health and longevity of their workspace. By highlighting the benefits of regular cleaning and maintenance, such as improved air quality, reduced allergens and bacteria, and longer-lasting surfaces and equipment, we can show potential clients why it's worth investing in regular cleaning services.</li>
<li>The role of technology in commercial cleaning. Technology is playing an increasingly important role in the commercial cleaning industry, with new tools and systems emerging all the time. By highlighting the latest technologies and innovations in the field of commercial cleaning, we can show potential clients that we are up-to-date on the latest trends and able to provide the most effective and efficient cleaning services.</li>
<li>The importance of using the right cleaning products. The cleaning products that we use can have a big impact on the effectiveness and safety of your cleaning services. By highlighting the importance of using the right cleaning products, we can show potential clients that we take the quality of our services seriously and are committed to providing the best possible results.</li>
<li>The role of customer service in commercial cleaning. Customer service is an important part of any business, and it's no different in the commercial cleaning industry. By highlighting the importance of customer service in commercial cleaning, we can show potential clients that we are committed to providing a high-quality, personalized service and that we are responsive to their needs and concerns.</li>
<li>The benefits of partnering with a commercial cleaning services provider. Many businesses may not realize the benefits of partnering with a commercial cleaning services provider, such as cost savings, flexibility, and peace of mind. By highlighting the advantages of partnering with a commercial cleaning services provider, we can show potential clients why they should choose us to be their cleaning partner.</li>
<li>The role of innovation and creativity in commercial cleaning. Innovation and creativity are important in any industry, and the commercial cleaning industry is no exception. By highlighting the role of innovation and creativity in commercial cleaning, we can show potential clients that we are constantly seeking new and better ways to provide effective and efficient cleaning services.</li>
<li>The importance of communication and collaboration in commercial cleaning. Communication and collaboration are essential for any successful business, and this is especially true in the commercial cleaning industry. By highlighting the importance of communication and collaboration in commercial cleaning, we can show potential clients that we are committed to working closely with them to understand their needs and provide the best possible cleaning services.</li>
<li>The challenges and opportunities of cleaning in the age of COVID-19. The COVID-19 pandemic has brought many challenges and opportunities for the commercial cleaning industry. By highlighting the challenges and opportunities of cleaning in the age of COVID-19, we can show potential clients that we are aware of the latest developments in the industry and that we are prepared to provide effective and safe cleaning services during this unprecedented time.</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/daft-punk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2022-10-12T15:43:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-12-21T19:40:59+01:00</updated>
  </entry>
</feed>
