<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/xsl/atom.xsl" media="all"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/interviewing/</id>
  <title>Akulina Nikitina - interviewing</title>
  <subtitle><![CDATA[A wordsmith, storyteller, visionary, and artist.]]></subtitle>
  <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/interviewing/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/interviewing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2018-04-10T00:53:07+02:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Akulina Nikitina</name>
    <uri>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/</uri>
  </author>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/interview-with-fabrizio-lapiana/</id>
    <title>Interview with Fabrizio Lapiana </title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Akulina: Italy is famous not only for its picturesque landscapes, delicious pasta and amazing wine. Many talented music producers are born there, so, it seems, Italian electronic scene is well developed. Being involved in techno movement from 90s, you may observe how Italian techno scene was formed and evolved. Has it changed greatly since that time? How would you describe current situation?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: The question is very complex and touches many aspects, not only musical but also social and economic. Surely the techno scene has changed a lot in our country as in the rest of the world. Talking just about music I could briefly say that everything was born in Rome between 1989 and 1991 thanks to a few artists, real pioneers, who characterized the sound of Rome and the first raves. It was something revolutionary, pure and spontaneous, that I lived only from the outside (thanks to some local radio stations, very popular at the time, and thanks to re-mix, dj record shop real fulcrum of the system) because I was just 15 or 16 years old. Today in our country these characteristics are gone, although there are still many excellent artists. Today, marketing has much more value than in the past.</p>
<p>Akulina: What does “underground” means to you?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: For me, undergound means pure, out of mainstream logics.</p>
<p>Akulina: How did you come on a decision to produce music?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: After many years as local dj I needed to do something more to express myself and my techno view and in 2008 I founded Attic Music and started producing.</p>
<p>Akulina: Tell us about Attic Music. What is the philosophy of label and your personal definition of techno? How do you select artists?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: There isn’t a philosophy or a concept. I just produce what I like and what I would play: tripping dark techno from deeper to banger, but also ambient and something different as for example the acid sound of Boston 168. </p>
<p>Akulina: Your last and yet a debut album “Intraverso” shows down-tempo, ambient influences and is beyond your usual style. Why did you choose this direction? Is there a story behind it?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: When I decided to work on my debut album I had no good times for private reasons so It was natural for me to express this side of my music.</p>
<p>Akulina: Do you believe in destiny and what is your biggest dream?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: I only believe in human strength and will. My dream is to do a radio show.</p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/interview-with-fabrizio-lapiana/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2018-04-10T00:53:07+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-12-20T01:45:27+01:00</updated>
  </entry>
</feed>
