<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/xsl/atom.xsl" media="all"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/portfolio-project/</id>
  <title>Akulina Nikitina - portfolio project</title>
  <subtitle><![CDATA[A wordsmith, storyteller, visionary, and artist.]]></subtitle>
  <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/portfolio-project/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/tags/portfolio-project/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2022-10-12T15:43:00+02:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Akulina Nikitina</name>
    <uri>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/</uri>
  </author>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/daft-punk/</id>
    <title>Content Plan for Commercial Cleaning Company</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 id="content-plan-for-commercial-cleaning-company">Content plan for commercial cleaning company.</h2>
<ol>
<li>Develop a series of FAQs that address common questions and concerns about commercial cleaning. These could include questions about the safety and effectiveness of cleaning products, the types of services we offer, and the process for booking and scheduling cleaning services. By providing answers to these common questions, we can help potential clients understand our services and make an informed decision.</li>
<li>Create a series of &quot;before and after&quot; photos that showcase the impact of our cleaning services. These photos could include images of dirty and cluttered spaces that have been transformed by our team's cleaning efforts. By highlighting the dramatic improvements that our services can provide, we can show potential clients the value of our services and build trust and credibility.</li>
<li>Develop a series of social media posts that provide tips and advice on maintaining a clean and healthy workspace. These could include quick and easy cleaning hacks, product recommendations, and general advice on how to create a clean and comfortable work environment. By sharing this valuable information on social media, we can engage with potential clients and build our online presence.</li>
<li>Write a series of articles that explore the latest trends and developments in commercial cleaning. These could include articles on new cleaning technologies, eco-friendly cleaning products, and innovative cleaning methods. By staying up-to-date on the latest developments in the industry, we can position ourself as an expert and thought leader in the field of commercial cleaning.</li>
</ol>
<h2 id="ideas-for-articles">Ideas for articles.</h2>
<ol>
<li>The importance of regular cleaning and maintenance. Many businesses may not realize the importance of regular cleaning and maintenance for the health and longevity of their workspace. By highlighting the benefits of regular cleaning and maintenance, such as improved air quality, reduced allergens and bacteria, and longer-lasting surfaces and equipment, we can show potential clients why it's worth investing in regular cleaning services.</li>
<li>The role of technology in commercial cleaning. Technology is playing an increasingly important role in the commercial cleaning industry, with new tools and systems emerging all the time. By highlighting the latest technologies and innovations in the field of commercial cleaning, we can show potential clients that we are up-to-date on the latest trends and able to provide the most effective and efficient cleaning services.</li>
<li>The importance of using the right cleaning products. The cleaning products that we use can have a big impact on the effectiveness and safety of your cleaning services. By highlighting the importance of using the right cleaning products, we can show potential clients that we take the quality of our services seriously and are committed to providing the best possible results.</li>
<li>The role of customer service in commercial cleaning. Customer service is an important part of any business, and it's no different in the commercial cleaning industry. By highlighting the importance of customer service in commercial cleaning, we can show potential clients that we are committed to providing a high-quality, personalized service and that we are responsive to their needs and concerns.</li>
<li>The benefits of partnering with a commercial cleaning services provider. Many businesses may not realize the benefits of partnering with a commercial cleaning services provider, such as cost savings, flexibility, and peace of mind. By highlighting the advantages of partnering with a commercial cleaning services provider, we can show potential clients why they should choose us to be their cleaning partner.</li>
<li>The role of innovation and creativity in commercial cleaning. Innovation and creativity are important in any industry, and the commercial cleaning industry is no exception. By highlighting the role of innovation and creativity in commercial cleaning, we can show potential clients that we are constantly seeking new and better ways to provide effective and efficient cleaning services.</li>
<li>The importance of communication and collaboration in commercial cleaning. Communication and collaboration are essential for any successful business, and this is especially true in the commercial cleaning industry. By highlighting the importance of communication and collaboration in commercial cleaning, we can show potential clients that we are committed to working closely with them to understand their needs and provide the best possible cleaning services.</li>
<li>The challenges and opportunities of cleaning in the age of COVID-19. The COVID-19 pandemic has brought many challenges and opportunities for the commercial cleaning industry. By highlighting the challenges and opportunities of cleaning in the age of COVID-19, we can show potential clients that we are aware of the latest developments in the industry and that we are prepared to provide effective and safe cleaning services during this unprecedented time.</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/daft-punk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2022-10-12T15:43:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-12-21T19:10:41+01:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/doom/</id>
    <title>Freedom Art Shop </title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 id="our-philosophy">Our Philosophy.</h2>
<p>The Ukrainian people are fighting for their freedom and independence. They're fighting for a country where they can speak their own language, have their own culture, and brag about who they are. We are a company that is dedicated to the idea of freedom. We believe that all humans should have the ability to be free and live life in peace. </p>
<p>We are Ukrainians. We are strong. We are fighting for our country and for our freedom! And this is something worth supporting! What better way to do that than with art? Digital art is not just a trend, but it's an integral part of the future of creativity. </p>
<p>This shop offers art illustrations to help those who are fighting for Ukraine with a portion of profit going to fund Ukrainian army. You can show your support by contributing or making a donation.</p>
<h2 id="digital-art-description-for-twitter-posts">Digital Art Description for Twitter posts.</h2>
<ul>
<li>Freedom is a universal human right. What does it mean to you? What does it mean to us? To Ukraine? To the world? This digital illustration depicts the struggle of Ukrainian people for their freedom and independence.</li>
<li>War is a painful reality that many people face. This digital illustration depicts the story of Ukrainian struggle for freedom and independence. It is an expression of the feelings that many Ukrainians and people around the world felt about Russia's invasion.</li>
<li>War is not a game. It's not something to be taken lightly, or something to be glorified. It's a serious matter that affects the lives of so many people. This artwork is meant to remind people of the horrors of war and the devastation it can bring. This artwork is a call for peace!</li>
<li>In the struggle for values, truth is born. Art is a powerful medium that can be used to express truth and share it with others. Whether you're an artist or not, we want to help you find your truth through art.</li>
<li>This digital art is a reminder that freedom is worth fighting for and that we must fight for it. We will never forget what it's like to be free.</li>
<li>With the rise of new tyrannical regimes and a general increase in global authoritarianism, it is more important than ever to remember that our desire for freedom is what will ultimately save us.</li>
<li>Freedom is what makes humans unique. It's the desire to be free that inspires revolutions and protest movements. It's what enables humans to rise and take control of their destiny.</li>
<li>Freedom is worth fighting for, and dying for, and living for.The desire to be free is the most important thing in the world. You can take our lives, but you'll never take away the desire to be free.</li>
<li>We are not the only ones who refuse to surrender. We are not the only ones who will never give up. We are not the only ones who refuse to be silenced.</li>
<li>We will stand up for what we believe in. We will speak out when we see injustice. We will be brave enough to take a stand and say, “I am not afraid of you”. We refuse to be silenced by fear, or oppression, or violence, or hate.</li>
<li>No matter how many battles we win, or how many lives we take, the desire to be free will never die. It's in our blood.</li>
<li>The idea of freedom is what binds us together as a nation. And it's part of who we are as people. We're not born with the desire for freedom - it's something that has to be fought for and protected every day. ⁣⁣</li>
<li>“The desire to be free is one of the deepest and most powerful yearnings of the human soul.”- Nelson Mandela. The will to be free is stronger than any bullet.</li>
<li>We believe that good always wins. And we’re here to make sure of it. It’s time to take a stand for what's right.</li>
<li>Life is full of ups and downs and it's easy to feel like you are fighting a losing battle. It's important not to give up, because ultimately good will prevail.</li>
<li>A warrior of light is someone who fights for his freedom and the future. He is not afraid to stand up for what he believes in, even if it means fighting for it. He never gives up, and always stands strong against adversity.</li>
<li>We are not here to be the victims, but the victors. We are not here to be defeated, but to be victorious.</li>
<li>“The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams.”- Eleanor Roosevelt. Stand up for what you believe in, fight for what you love, and be the voice of the voiceless.</li>
<li>This illustration is haunting and beautiful and it explores the depths of human emotion, from sorrow to rage to hope.</li>
</ul>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/doom/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2022-06-23T00:00:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-12-21T19:10:41+01:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/princess-mononoke/</id>
    <title>Do you believe in the power of Tarot cards?</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>*﻿The task was to write up to ten generalized predictions based on different card combinations, with a short, effective lead for the NFT project. Here are several examples based on the Tarot card meaning.</p>
<h3 id="do-you-believe-in-the-power-of-tarot-cards">Do you believe in the power of Tarot cards?</h3>
<p>The Tarot cards are a symbol of the past, present, and future. They have been used as tools of divination and guidance for centuries. “The Eternal Journey” is a kit of design Tarot cards that goes together with a personal prediction. It's an easy way to get started in the world of tarot and it's a great gift for someone who is interested in this spiritual practice.</p>
<p>Let your future unfold before your eyes.</p>
<p>Prediction for - The Lovers, The Emperor, The Chariot.</p>
<ul>
<li>The Lovers is about the connection between two people. The Emperor is about authority, control, and power. The Chariot is about being in charge of one's life journey. What does this mean for you? It means that it's time to take control of your life and stop waiting for others to make things happen for you. It's time to be a leader and not a follower. Live your life on your terms and be the best version of yourself!</li>
</ul>
<p>Prediction for - The Tower, Wheel of Fortune, Temperance.</p>
<ul>
<li>Skyrocketing success is yours to enjoy, if you dare and grab the moment! You’ve reached a turning point. Wheel of Fortune has blessed you with a new opportunity. See trees changing colours as they prepare for winter? That’s how your life feels right now. You need to trust the Universe and seize the day! The Tower is the doorway to opportunity and dynamism, but can also make or break our stability and direction. Temperance is there to unify conflicting energies, and heal ailments of previous cycles.</li>
</ul>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/princess-mononoke/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2021-04-06T00:00:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-12-21T19:10:41+01:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/interview-with-fabrizio-lapiana/</id>
    <title>Interview with Fabrizio Lapiana </title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Akulina: Italy is famous not only for its picturesque landscapes, delicious pasta and amazing wine. Many talented music producers are born there, so, it seems, Italian electronic scene is well developed. Being involved in techno movement from 90s, you may observe how Italian techno scene was formed and evolved. Has it changed greatly since that time? How would you describe current situation?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: The question is very complex and touches many aspects, not only musical but also social and economic. Surely the techno scene has changed a lot in our country as in the rest of the world. Talking just about music I could briefly say that everything was born in Rome between 1989 and 1991 thanks to a few artists, real pioneers, who characterized the sound of Rome and the first raves. It was something revolutionary, pure and spontaneous, that I lived only from the outside (thanks to some local radio stations, very popular at the time, and thanks to re-mix, dj record shop real fulcrum of the system) because I was just 15 or 16 years old. Today in our country these characteristics are gone, although there are still many excellent artists. Today, marketing has much more value than in the past.</p>
<p>Akulina: What does “underground” means to you?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: For me, undergound means pure, out of mainstream logics.</p>
<p>Akulina: How did you come on a decision to produce music?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: After many years as local dj I needed to do something more to express myself and my techno view and in 2008 I founded Attic Music and started producing.</p>
<p>Akulina: Tell us about Attic Music. What is the philosophy of label and your personal definition of techno? How do you select artists?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: There isn’t a philosophy or a concept. I just produce what I like and what I would play: tripping dark techno from deeper to banger, but also ambient and something different as for example the acid sound of Boston 168. </p>
<p>Akulina: Your last and yet a debut album “Intraverso” shows down-tempo, ambient influences and is beyond your usual style. Why did you choose this direction? Is there a story behind it?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: When I decided to work on my debut album I had no good times for private reasons so It was natural for me to express this side of my music.</p>
<p>Akulina: Do you believe in destiny and what is your biggest dream?</p>
<p>F﻿abrizio: I only believe in human strength and will. My dream is to do a radio show.</p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="https://cecilapp.github.io/the-butler/blog/interview-with-fabrizio-lapiana/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2018-04-10T00:53:07+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-12-21T19:10:41+01:00</updated>
  </entry>
</feed>
